{
    "Questions": [
      {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "What is H2O2 commonly known as?",
        "choices" : ["Water", "Hydrogen peroxide","Salt"],
        "right-answer": "Hydrogen peroxide"
      },
      {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "Which of the following elements is not a liquid around room temperature?",
        "choices" : [" Magnesium", "Bromine","Mercury"],
        "right-answer": "Magnesium"
      },
      {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "Which of the followings does not contain potassium?",
        "choices" : ["Soap", "Gunpowder","Bread"],
        "right-answer": "Bread"
      },
      {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "What do we call the process in which an atomâ€™s nucleus splits into smaller elements?",
        "choices" : ["Nuclear fusion", "Nuclear fission","Nuclear reaction"],
        "right-answer": "Nuclear fission"
      },
      {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "What is the role of salt in a saline solution or a solution of saltwater?",
        "choices" : ["Sol", "Solvent","Solute"],
        "right-answer": "Solute"
      },
      {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "Which of the followings is not a rare-earth element?",
        "choices" : ["Terbium", "Gold","Lanthanum"],
        "right-answer": "2"
      },
      {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "If we fill a glass with ice cubes and water. What will occur when the ice melts?",
        "choices" : [" The water level remains the same", "The water level increases slightly","The water level decreases slightly"],
        "right-answer": "The water level decreases slightly"
      },
      {
        "id": "8",
        "question": "Based on the pH level, how can we describe milk?",
        "choices" : ["Slightly acidic", "Neutral","Slightly basic"],
        "right-answer": " Slightly acidic"
      },
      {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "Which of the following elements is heavier than iron?",
        "choices" : ["Gold", "Manganese","Potassium"],
        "right-answer": "Gold"
      },
      {
        "id": "10",
        "question": " What does AMU stand for in chemistry?",
        "choices" : ["Atomic Matter Unit", " Atomic Mass Unit","Accelerated Mass Unit"],
        "right-answer": "Atomic Mass Unit"
      }
    ]
  }